Steven Kulp

San Diego, CA 92104 sdkulp@gmail.com (503) 475-2777

Full-Stack Web Developer

stevenkulp.com github.com/stevenkulp linkedin.com/in/steven.kulp

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer and UX/UI enthusiast with a passion for creativity and a knack for problem-solving. A recent coding school graduate with contractor work experience who is looking to take his skills to the next level and grow long-term with a developer team. Backed by 4 years of additional office and project management experience.

Technical Skills

HTML5 · CSS3 · Javascript · React · Python · Ruby · Ruby on Rails · PostgreSQL · Photoshop · Illustrator

Experience

Web Developer (Contractor), PermitDocs (March 2019 - Current)

- · Created a Chrome browser extension to augment the PermitDocs platform into a user's web browsing experience.
- · Developed Python scripts to aggregate, read, filter, and store relevant documents and data for the platform.
- · Gained invaluable experience and knowledge as a result of working directly in the Web Development industry.

Web Developer (Student), LEARN Academy (November 2018 - March 2019)

- Built a variety of web and mobile applications using front-end and back-end programming languages.
- Created and solved detailed and complex logic problems through the use of critical thinking.
- 400+ hours of hands-on training via solo programming, pair programming, and mob programming.

Operations Associate, RSI Security (March 2018 - November 2018)

- Managed Accounts Payable, tracking all outgoing expenses and eliminating/preventing unnecessary spending.
- Coordinated and researched events and opportunities to maximize sales opportunities and company presence.
- · Evaluated company metrics and KPIs to pinpoint areas of strength as well as areas for improvement.

Assistant Property Manager, C&R Real Estate (June 2016 - March 2018)

- Recipient of "2017 Award of Excellence" for strong project management skills during massive renovation project.
- Maintained an exceptional retention rate of current tenants, with consistent resident satisfaction.
- Implemented sales and marketing campaigns to improve property visibility, minimizing unit turnaround times.

Account Manager, Sirennet (December 2014 - June 2016)

- · Maintained client accounts, serving as the primary point of contact for the client.
- · Constructed winning bids for client projects, and arranged timely and accurate deliveries of large/complex orders...
- Managed company's retail Amazon vendor page, leading to increased revenue and seller rating.

Various Retail Positions, Quiznos Subs, Macy's, Wizer's Market (May 2007 - December 2014)

Education

B.A. Psychology and Graphic Design, Portland State University (2007 - 2012)